A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Culture Program, Office Files of Linn F.C. Cary FA533
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Education and Culture Program, 1968-1985; III
  - Subject Files, III.2
    - Indigenous Peoples -- Cultural Survival, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Institute for Journalism Education, 1983 (Box 9)
    - International Division -- Support for the Arts Grant List, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - International Education -- Association for World Education (University for Peace), 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - International Education -- Berlin Science Center, Universities and International Studies, 1983 (Box 10)
    - International Fellowship Programs, 1982 (Box 10)
    - International Grantmaking in Education and Culture -- Council on Foundations, 1979-1983 (Box 10)
    - International Grantmaking in Education and Culture -- National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - International University Foundation Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Inuit Circumpolar Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Journalism/Communications, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - Manuscript Preservation, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Mayleas, Ruth Files -- Memoranda Re: Arts, Culture, Literacy Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Museology/Manuscript Preservation, 1978-1984 (Box 10)
    - National Chicano Council for Higher Education (NCCHE) -- Summary of Grant and Notes, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Native American Hopi Tribe -- Slides (incl. Oneida Reservation and Warm Springs, Oregon) (Box 10)
    - Native American Task Force (incl. photographs), 1985 (Box 10)
    - Nguyen Quynh ( Vietnam Culture Journal), 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Officers Meeting -- Agendas, Notes, 1981-1983 (Box 10)
    - Performing/Plastic Arts, 1983-1985 (Box 10)
    - Planning -- Cultural Preservation, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
    - Planning -- Cultural Preservation, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Popular Education and Culture, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Program Development -- Arts -- Grant Proposals and Foundation Work, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Program Development -- Arts in Society -- Prisons, Schools, Communities, etc., 1982 (Box 10)
    - Program Development -- Cultural Preservation -- Grant Proposals, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Program Development -- Education -- Grant Proposals and Foundation Work, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Program Development -- Faculty Development, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Program Development and Planning -- "A Selected Chronology of the Ford Foundation", circa 1980 (Box 10)
    - Program Planning -- Literacy, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Refugees and Migration -- Draft of "International Migration and Refugees" Ford Foundation Staff Paper, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Refugees and Migration -- Grant Proposals, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Refugees and Migration -- Recommendation for Grant Actions (RGAs), 1981 (Box 10)
    - Refugees and Migration -- Social Science Research Council -- Grant Proposals Re: Southeast Asian Refugees, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Resources/Organizations, 1981-1985 (Box 10)
    - RGAs (Recommendations for Grant Action) -- Examples, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Smithsonian Office of Folklife Programs, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Social Sciences, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Soedjatmoko, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Telephone Calls/Visits Re: Grant Requests, Meetings with Linn Cary, etc., 1983 (Box 11)
    - United Nations Conference on Housing Rehabilitation (1 of 2), 1982 February (Box 11)
    - United Nations Conference on Housing Rehabilitation (2 of 2), 1982 February (Box 11)
    - Urban Poverty/DCP, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Urban Poverty -- India and Greece and Conference Reports, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Urban Poverty -- Latin America, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Urban Programs Overseas FY 1982 Forward Planning, 1981 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Caribbean Cultural Center, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Center for American Culture Studies (Columbia), 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Studio Museum in Harlem, 1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- American Association for State and Local History, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Appalshop, 1976-1983 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Center for Southern Folklore, 1978-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Center for the Study of Southern Culture at the University of Mississippi, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Highlander Center, 1981-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- MACE (Mississippi Action for Community Education)/Delta Arts, 1981 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Trip Planning Reports to Appalachia and the Deep South, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Appalachia and the Deep South -- Notebook, circa 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Southwest and West -- General -- Southwest Trip, 1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Southwest and West -- Heard Museum, Arizona, circa 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Cultural Preservation -- Southwest and West -- Institute of American Indian Art, 1983 (Box 11)
    - USIAP Program Planning -- Re: Cultural Preservation, 1983-1985 (Box 11)
    - Women's Programming -- Catharine Stimpson Research and Paper Writing on Women, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Women's Programming -- Feminist Press (Florence Howe) Proposal for Funding, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Women's Programming -- Feminist Press, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Women's Programming -- National Council for Research on Women -- Grants, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Women's Programming -- Bank Street/Work and Family Life, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Ford Foundation Grants (National and International), 1960s-1980s (1 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Ford Foundation Grants (National and International), 1960s-1980s (2 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Ford Foundation Grants (National and International), 1960s-1980s (3 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Ford Foundation Information Papers on Women, 1980-1982 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Ford Foundation Publications on Women, 1975-1980 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Integration of Gender Concerns in Overseas Development Curriculum and Research, 1981-1984 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- International Women's Studies, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Memoranda/Field Office Reports on Women, 1982-1984 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Publications Re: Women and their Work and Education (publications funded by Ford Foundation), 1976-1980 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Report (published), "Women in the World-A Ford Foundation Position Paper", 1980 November (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Reports Re: Women and Women's Movement, 1979-1982 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Scholarship on Women, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Equity Action League (WEAL), 1982 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Meeting -- Delhi, 1982 April (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Meeting Follow-up, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Meeting Notes, 1985 October 7 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Group -- Nairobi Women's Conference (Jul 1985) and Other Women's Program Group Meetings -- Memoranda, Meeting Materials, etc., 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Group -- 1985 Conference on Women -- Planning Materials and Papers, 1979-1983 (Box 12)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Group -- Memoranda, Reports, Notes Re: Meetings, Foundation Work, Grants, Travel, Conferences, etc., 1980-1981 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Program Group -- National Affairs -- Women's Program Review, Jan 1981 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Research and Education Institute, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- Women's Studies -- U.S., 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- Women in Development (WID) -- Reports Re: Women and Development, Technology, Media, etc. and Gender Inequality, 1977-1984 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- Special Appropriation for Women Report, FY 1984, 1980-1984 (Box 13)
    - Women's Programming -- General -- Memoranda Re: Grants, Grantees, WPG Meetings, etc., 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - World Crafts Council, 1983 (Box 13)